[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "You've overtaken him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "overtaken", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Do you feel uncomfortable about that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "uncomfortable", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I mean, it's -", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "If you were to come on and I was to ask you, honestly, what is your talent, would you -- would you have any?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "to", "come", "on", "and", "I", "was", "to", "ask", "you", ",", "honestly", ",", "what", "is", "your", "talent", ",", "would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "have", "any", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I would absolutely say that marketing is a skill.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "absolutely", "say", "that", "marketing", "is", "a", "skill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "-- we're laughing all the way to the bank?", "question_tokens": ["--", "we", "'re", "laughing", "all", "the", "way", "to", "the", "bank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "It doesn't hurt me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "hurt", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Yes, what do you put on your passport?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "what", "do", "you", "put", "on", "your", "passport", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "It changes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "changes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Teacher?", "question_tokens": ["Teacher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Something that I don't do.", "answer_tokens": ["Something", "that", "I", "do", "n't", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Do you think you are normal underneath all this gloss?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "are", "normal", "underneath", "all", "this", "gloss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "You're liable for the petrol and the gas and the insurance, everything, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "liable", "for", "the", "petrol", "and", "the", "gas", "and", "the", "insurance", ",", "everything", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "If you were to sum up your brand in one word, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "to", "sum", "up", "your", "brand", "in", "one", "word", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "OURTNEY KARDASHIAN: That's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["OURTNEY", "KARDASHIAN", ":", "That", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Brand for the fans?", "question_tokens": ["Brand", "for", "the", "fans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Everything they ask us -- because I think I'm -- I know -- and my sisters were heavily involved in our blogs and our Twitter and our Facebooks.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "they", "ask", "us", "--", "because", "I", "think", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "know", "--", "and", "my", "sisters", "were", "heavily", "involved", "in", "our", "blogs", "and", "our", "Twitter", "and", "our", "Facebooks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "You're not stupid, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "stupid", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "How much of your brand is based around body image?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "your", "brand", "is", "based", "around", "body", "image", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I think a lot of it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "I am, but I'm five feet tall.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "five", "feet", "tall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Are these life-sized?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "life-sized", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "We're going to find out, aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "find", "out", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "CD", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Who's taller?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "taller", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Actually, you're -- yes, your one's taller than you.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "you", "'re", "--", "yes", ",", "your", "one", "'s", "taller", "than", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Like, what do I like and don't like?", "question_tokens": ["Like", ",", "what", "do", "I", "like", "and", "do", "n't", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "What do you like and don't like about your own --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "like", "and", "do", "n't", "like", "about", "your", "own", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "I mean, is that -- do you see that as a plus?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "that", "--", "do", "you", "see", "that", "as", "a", "plus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Kim, when you were young, you hated that, right?", "question_tokens": ["Kim", ",", "when", "you", "were", "young", ",", "you", "hated", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I hated it, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hated", "it", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Are they real?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "real", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "They are real.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "real", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Completely, 100 percent real?", "question_tokens": ["Completely", ",", "100", "percent", "real", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "They're completely, 100 percent real.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "completely", ",", "100", "percent", "real", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "They're fake?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "fake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "You've had -- you've had surgery?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "had", "--", "you", "'ve", "had", "surgery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "And you haven't?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "have", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "You have like I have an ugly day, when you look in the mirror and you're, like, oh, my God.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "like", "I", "have", "an", "ugly", "day", ",", "when", "you", "look", "in", "the", "mirror", "and", "you", "'re", ",", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "my", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What is the part of you that you sometimes say, I wish that was better?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "part", "of", "you", "that", "you", "sometimes", "say", ",", "I", "wish", "that", "was", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "When I -- when I'm a little heavier because my body is petite, I see -- go to, you know, my thighs or something.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "--", "when", "I", "'m", "a", "little", "heavier", "because", "my", "body", "is", "petite", ",", "I", "see", "--", "go", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "thighs", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "What are you guys doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "guys", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Obviously in the counterclockwise bed swirl, Kim.", "answer_tokens": ["Obviously", "in", "the", "counterclockwise", "bed", "swirl", ",", "Kim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 331, "question": "I mean, you're -- what is taking New York mean?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "--", "what", "is", "taking", "New", "York", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, we --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Where are you taking it?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "taking", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "We are taking it to a Kardashian level, which basically means that --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "taking", "it", "to", "a", "Kardashian", "level", ",", "which", "basically", "means", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kourtney", "Khloe"], "LOCATION": ["L.A.", "Miami"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What's that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "We're just opening up a clothing store, which is our store, Dash, that we -- we started one in L.A. And Kourtney and Khloe took Miami to open one up there.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "just", "opening", "up", "a", "clothing", "store", ",", "which", "is", "our", "store", ",", "Dash", ",", "that", "we", "--", "we", "started", "one", "in", "L.A.", "And", "Kourtney", "and", "Khloe", "took", "Miami", "to", "open", "one", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "(INAUDIBLE), why are you first on the title?", "question_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "why", "are", "you", "first", "on", "the", "title", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Because I'm the oldest and the best.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "the", "oldest", "and", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Doesn't that make her the biggest star?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "that", "make", "her", "the", "biggest", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Does that annoy you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "annoy", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kourtney"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NN", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Kourtney could care -- I always say to everyone, Kourtney could care less about fame, about anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Kourtney", "could", "care", "--", "I", "always", "say", "to", "everyone", ",", "Kourtney", "could", "care", "less", "about", "fame", ",", "about", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "That she pulled the baby out herself?", "question_tokens": ["That", "she", "pulled", "the", "baby", "out", "herself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "No, the whole thing is extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "the", "whole", "thing", "is", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do you expect any privacy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "expect", "any", "privacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, that -- well, that's why I didn't want the cameras there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "--", "well", ",", "that", "'s", "why", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "the", "cameras", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Where was all the screaming and the yelling?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "all", "the", "screaming", "and", "the", "yelling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Do you ever feel, you know, that you have any right to complain about paparazzi or intrusion into your private life once you've done that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "feel", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "you", "have", "any", "right", "to", "complain", "about", "paparazzi", "or", "intrusion", "into", "your", "private", "life", "once", "you", "'ve", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I don't know if I've a right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'ve", "a", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Is anything off limits in your life, given you've put it all out there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "anything", "off", "limits", "in", "your", "life", ",", "given", "you", "'ve", "put", "it", "all", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "I'm assuming you've saved that to tell me all about it, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "assuming", "you", "'ve", "saved", "that", "to", "tell", "me", "all", "about", "it", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "I know you are, a big fan, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", "you", "are", ",", "a", "big", "fan", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "A little.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "I mean, is he as evil to work with as I would hope he would be?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "he", "as", "evil", "to", "work", "with", "as", "I", "would", "hope", "he", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Ryan is so easy to talk to.", "answer_tokens": ["Ryan", "is", "so", "easy", "to", "talk", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Any bad points?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "bad", "points", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Is there anything you wouldn't do for the cameras?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "you", "would", "n't", "do", "for", "the", "cameras", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "I mean, would you -- would you record your own death?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "record", "your", "own", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "There's a lot that we wouldn't show.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "lot", "that", "we", "would", "n't", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Like, I know in our New York season, I didn't feel comfortable having my son on the show.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", ",", "I", "know", "in", "our", "New", "York", "season", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "feel", "comfortable", "having", "my", "son", "on", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I would never move in with anyone unless I was engaged or married.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "never", "move", "in", "with", "anyone", "unless", "I", "was", "engaged", "or", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Have I stumbled upon a bigger scoop?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "stumbled", "upon", "a", "bigger", "scoop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "You're not engaged?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "engaged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "So, you're not moving in with him?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "moving", "in", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 532, "question": "You, just together?", "question_tokens": ["You", ",", "just", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well, Scott has his -- our place here, so --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Scott", "has", "his", "--", "our", "place", "here", ",", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Can you trust men, given what's happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "trust", "men", ",", "given", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I think that the way that I am -- I'm such a hopeless romantic --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "the", "way", "that", "I", "am", "--", "I", "'m", "such", "a", "hopeless", "romantic", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "They'd have to believe in God?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'d", "have", "to", "believe", "in", "God", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Dark?", "question_tokens": ["Dark", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I like tall, even though I'm five feet tall.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "tall", ",", "even", "though", "I", "'m", "five", "feet", "tall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "They're all these beefcakes, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "all", "these", "beefcakes", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "So how tall is your current guy?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "tall", "is", "your", "current", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Six-foot-nine.", "answer_tokens": ["Six-foot-nine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Is he really?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "And how tall are you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "tall", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Five-foot-three.", "answer_tokens": ["Five-foot-three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Be like a little Chihuahua if he takes you for a walk, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Be", "like", "a", "little", "Chihuahua", "if", "he", "takes", "you", "for", "a", "walk", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Oh, it's the best way to feel skinny.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "to", "feel", "skinny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chihuahua"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Tiny and skinny.", "answer_tokens": ["Tiny", "and", "skinny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Are you happy that Kim is now happy?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "that", "Kim", "is", "now", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I'm happy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "ORGAN: Do you feel protective, like a little big sister?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "feel", "protective", ",", "like", "a", "little", "big", "sister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "A little.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Is he behaving himself now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "behaving", "himself", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Depp"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Who do you think are the real hunks out there?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "are", "the", "real", "hunks", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Love Johnny Depp.", "answer_tokens": ["Love", "Johnny", "Depp", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "So are you going to get married?", "question_tokens": ["So", "are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "One day, I hope to get married, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "day", ",", "I", "hope", "to", "get", "married", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Sooner rather than later, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Sooner", "rather", "than", "later", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "What about for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 677, "question": "So you want to give your little one a happily married setup?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "want", "to", "give", "your", "little", "one", "a", "happily", "married", "setup", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I do, but I just think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "but", "I", "just", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "-- and proposed, would you say \"yes\"?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "proposed", ",", "would", "you", "say", "``", "yes", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "``", "NNS", "''", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Ballas"], "LOCATION": ["Bristol"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "''", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What would you say if I said \"Sarah Palin\"?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "if", "I", "said", "``", "Sarah", "Palin", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "I was on \"Dancing with the Stars\", and my partner was Mark Ballas, who was Bristol's partner.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "on", "``", "Dancing", "with", "the", "Stars", "''", ",", "and", "my", "partner", "was", "Mark", "Ballas", ",", "who", "was", "Bristol", "'s", "partner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Do you think that she's a good thing for America as a politician?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "she", "'s", "a", "good", "thing", "for", "America", "as", "a", "politician", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "You know, I know she gets a lot of flack, so I -- I don't know, I just tend to -- I don't typically like to say anything if I don't really have an opinion either way, to be honest.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "know", "she", "gets", "a", "lot", "of", "flack", ",", "so", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "just", "tend", "to", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "typically", "like", "to", "say", "anything", "if", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "have", "an", "opinion", "either", "way", ",", "to", "be", "honest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Is he doing a good job?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "doing", "a", "good", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I think he's doing a good job.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "a", "good", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "man", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "He was definitely the strict parent when it was, you know, him and my mom.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "definitely", "the", "strict", "parent", "when", "it", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "him", "and", "my", "mom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 739, "question": "What kind of impact did that have on you two, do you think, looking back?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "impact", "did", "that", "have", "on", "you", "two", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "looking", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "We were --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "What would your dad have made, do you think, of the success you've made of yourselves?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "dad", "have", "made", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "of", "the", "success", "you", "'ve", "made", "of", "yourselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "I think he would have been extremely proud of us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "would", "have", "been", "extremely", "proud", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "If you got the chance to talk to him again, what would you say that, perhaps, you never got to say when he was alive?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "got", "the", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "him", "again", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "that", ",", "perhaps", ",", "you", "never", "got", "to", "say", "when", "he", "was", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I think we did a really good job at telling him exactly how we felt, especially right before he passed away.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "did", "a", "really", "good", "job", "at", "telling", "him", "exactly", "how", "we", "felt", ",", "especially", "right", "before", "he", "passed", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Who says that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "says", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I just did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "Yes, or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "What, do you want to talk yen or pounds or Chilean pesos?", "question_tokens": ["What", ",", "do", "you", "want", "to", "talk", "yen", "or", "pounds", "or", "Chilean", "pesos", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Combined, I would say, I don't talk dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["Combined", ",", "I", "would", "say", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "talk", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Kim is.", "answer_tokens": ["Kim", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 811, "question": "Where are we going, here, 10, 30, 60, 80?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "we", "going", ",", "here", ",", "10", ",", "30", ",", "60", ",", "80", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 812, "answer": "I don't think it's ever appropriate to talk money.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "ever", "appropriate", "to", "talk", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 820, "question": "Do you really?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 821, "answer": "Every year.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "Ten percent of all your money?", "question_tokens": ["Ten", "percent", "of", "all", "your", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Do you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "I'm going to now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 833, "question": "So you've given away millions, then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "given", "away", "millions", ",", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 834, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 836, "question": "Which church do you give it to?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "church", "do", "you", "give", "it", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 837, "answer": "There's a charity that I work with a lot that I donate money all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "charity", "that", "I", "work", "with", "a", "lot", "that", "I", "donate", "money", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dream Foundation"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "Do you want to name it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "name", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "The Dream Foundation.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Dream", "Foundation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "So you've given them millions?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "given", "them", "millions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "And we have -- my mom has helped create a church.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "we", "have", "--", "my", "mom", "has", "helped", "create", "a", "church", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "JJR", "NN", ",", "RBR", "NNS", "''", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 846, "question": "I mean, do you like being really rich?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "like", "being", "really", "rich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 847, "answer": "I think that it definitely -- when people say -- I mean, I get the statement when they say \"more money, more problems\" -- I definitely get that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "definitely", "--", "when", "people", "say", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "get", "the", "statement", "when", "they", "say", "``", "more", "money", ",", "more", "problems", "''", "--", "I", "definitely", "get", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 854, "question": "Who's the most generous?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "most", "generous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 855, "answer": "We all try and make --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "all", "try", "and", "make", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Who's the one who always says \"oh no, I've left my purse behind\"?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "one", "who", "always", "says", "``", "oh", "no", ",", "I", "'ve", "left", "my", "purse", "behind", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "``", "UH", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "Kourtney.", "answer_tokens": ["Kourtney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "Kourtney is becoming a bit of a problem here financially, I think, isn't she?", "question_tokens": ["Kourtney", "is", "becoming", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "problem", "here", "financially", ",", "I", "think", ",", "is", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "Yes, she is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "she", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 869, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 870, "answer": "No, it's fun, but I love to also --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "fun", ",", "but", "I", "love", "to", "also", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "What's the most extravagant thing either of you has ever bought for yourselves?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "most", "extravagant", "thing", "either", "of", "you", "has", "ever", "bought", "for", "yourselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "Kim does it daily for herself.", "answer_tokens": ["Kim", "does", "it", "daily", "for", "herself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "OURTNEY KARDASHIAN: A watch for yourself?", "question_tokens": ["OURTNEY", "KARDASHIAN", ":", "A", "watch", "for", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 884, "question": "How much would that be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 885, "answer": "115.", "answer_tokens": ["115", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 886, "question": "115?", "question_tokens": ["115", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 887, "answer": "Thousand.", "answer_tokens": ["Thousand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "Dollars?", "question_tokens": ["Dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "One hundred fifteen thousand dollars for a watch?", "question_tokens": ["One", "hundred", "fifteen", "thousand", "dollars", "for", "a", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "Yes, but I got a really good deal on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "I", "got", "a", "really", "good", "deal", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 896, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd be in a position to spend 115 thousand dollars on a watch?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "you", "'d", "be", "in", "a", "position", "to", "spend", "115", "thousand", "dollars", "on", "a", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 897, "answer": "I don't do that stuff for myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "do", "that", "stuff", "for", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["115 thousand dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "Or you haven't got as much money as Kim?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "you", "have", "n't", "got", "as", "much", "money", "as", "Kim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "Well, I don't have as much money as Kim.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "as", "much", "money", "as", "Kim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "You do this with your mum, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "this", "with", "your", "mum", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "Ladies, do you ever fear over-exposure?", "question_tokens": ["Ladies", ",", "do", "you", "ever", "fear", "over-exposure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "Sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 927, "question": "You know, and in your own way, you're living the American dream, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "and", "in", "your", "own", "way", ",", "you", "'re", "living", "the", "American", "dream", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 928, "answer": "I would say so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor", "Ava Gardner"], "LOCATION": ["Sofia Loren"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 933, "question": "Who do you idolize?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "idolize", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 934, "answer": "I love women like Elizabeth Taylor and Sofia Loren and Ava Gardner.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "women", "like", "Elizabeth", "Taylor", "and", "Sofia", "Loren", "and", "Ava", "Gardner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Liz Taylor"]}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 943, "question": "He did?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 944, "answer": "-- if he just married Liz Taylor.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "if", "he", "just", "married", "Liz", "Taylor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 945, "question": "It would have made life so much easier, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "made", "life", "so", "much", "easier", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJR", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 946, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 962, "question": "The moment, if you got the chance, you'd relive again?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", ",", "if", "you", "got", "the", "chance", ",", "you", "'d", "relive", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 963, "answer": "I would say, having my son.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", ",", "having", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "What about you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "I would say, it was probably something that I didn't realize at the time, like a family ski trip with my dad and my mom.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", ",", "it", "was", "probably", "something", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "realize", "at", "the", "time", ",", "like", "a", "family", "ski", "trip", "with", "my", "dad", "and", "my", "mom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 972, "question": "That would be a special thing, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "a", "special", "thing", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 973, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 994, "question": "Do you design them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "design", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 995, "answer": "They are some of the most finest Italian designs in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "some", "of", "the", "most", "finest", "Italian", "designs", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 998, "question": "Have I got it in me?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "got", "it", "in", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 999, "answer": "I've seen one outfit, and it looks pretty snazzy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "seen", "one", "outfit", ",", "and", "it", "looks", "pretty", "snazzy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1002, "question": "Do you think the whole British thing might work?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "whole", "British", "thing", "might", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1003, "answer": "A plus.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "plus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1005, "question": "Do you have a stylist?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "stylist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1006, "answer": "I'm beginning to think you may be the perfect person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "beginning", "to", "think", "you", "may", "be", "the", "perfect", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1007, "question": "You want to style me?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "style", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1008, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1025, "question": "Do you start stammering because you got so used to that voice?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "start", "stammering", "because", "you", "got", "so", "used", "to", "that", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1026, "answer": "We all stammer, actually, It's bizarre how contagious a stammer is.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "all", "stammer", ",", "actually", ",", "It", "'s", "bizarre", "how", "contagious", "a", "stammer", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]